<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visa Categories on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visa Categories on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Student Visa</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/student-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/student-visa/</guid>
      <description>Study Visa A student visa allows you to study full time in New Zealand. Students who are undertaking a course of 12 months or more are eligible to work for 20 hours per week and full time during Christmas Holidays. After graduating from a course that would qualify for points under the Skilled Migrant Category, students are eligible to apply for a Post Study Work Visa without an offer of employment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skilled Migrant Category (Residence)</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/skilled-migrant-category-residence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/skilled-migrant-category-residence/</guid>
      <description>The objective of the Skilled Migrant Category is to provide for the grant of residence to people who demonstrate that they have skills to fill identified shortages and opportunities in New Zealand. They are able to transfer those skills to New Zealand and link with local needs and opportunities and are able to demonstrate an ability to contribute to New Zealand both economically and socially. They are able to demonstrate an ability to successfully settle in New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Categories</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/family-categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/family-categories/</guid>
      <description>If you and your family may wish to be reunited in New Zealand, you need to apply for a relationship visa. Your brother, sister or parent must be eligible to sponsor you. You must be in one of the following categories:
Partner: you are the husband, wife, de-facto or civil union partner of a New Zealand citizen or resident visa or a temporary visa holder. Partners can apply for either partnership based work or visitor visa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visitor Visa</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/visitor-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/visitor-visa/</guid>
      <description>General Visitor Visa When you intend to stay temporarily in New Zealand, not study or work, you may need to apply for a Visitor’s visa. When you are outside New Zealand you need to apply for a Visitor’s Visa allowing you to travel to New Zealand. When you are granted a visa on arrival in New Zealand (stamp in your passport) you may remain in New Zealand for up to nine months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Categories</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/business-categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/business-categories/</guid>
      <description>Business Visa Business people have a choice in the type of application they wish to apply under that will allow them to work and gain residence in New Zealand.
Business people may use one of the following visas that will allow them to work and gain residence in New Zealand. The various criteria are described under each individual application type.
Entrepreneur Work Visa The New Zealand Government wishes to attract talented, enterprising, well-connected business people to invest and grow businesses in New Zealand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Visa</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/work-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/work-visa/</guid>
      <description>Essential Skills Work Visa This is a work visa based purely on skills and experience, and on the requirements of the employer.
This application may be subject to a Labour Market Check (LMC) with Work and Income NZ (WINZ) to ensure that local New Zealanders are protected.
When the offered salary is the same or higher than the median salary, you may be granted a 3 year work visa, and if lower, a 1 or 2 year work visa may be granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Resident Visa</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/2021-resident-visa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/2021-resident-visa/</guid>
      <description>If you are a work visa holder in New Zealand or a critical purpose visitor visa holder you may be eligible for residence under the new 2021 Resident Visa. Some critical purpose visa holders arriving in New Zealand between 30 September 2021 and 31 July 2022 on long term visas may also be eligible for the new visa.
2021 Resident Visa Eligibility Partners and dependent children, including those currently outside New Zealand, can be included in residence applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variation of Conditions (VOC)</title>
      <link>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/variation-of-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pravasiconsultants.com/visa-categories/variation-of-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Student Visa Holders You may be able to apply for a variation of conditions to allow you to change the course you are studying, the education provider you are studying with or the location of your study, or to allow to you to work part time and/or full-time during your holidays.
Work Visa Holders You may apply for a variation of conditions to allow you to change your occupation, your employer or your place of employment, or to study part-time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
